[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Tanya Tucker perform the song Man with 18 Wheels for the Black Dog soundtrack?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the book on which the war film The Longest Day is based?", "correct_answer": "Cornelius Ryan", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Seddon", "Roamin Gary", "James Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which stage of the virus life-cycle restricts it to infecting only a certain species (or group) of organisms?", "correct_answer": "Attachment to host", "incorrect_answers": ["Assembly of viral particles", "Replication of the viral DNA or RNA", "Release of viral particles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alan Rickman plays Colonel Brandon in the 1995 movie Sense and Sensibility.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which Bourne movie/movies is there a shootout  in Moscow?", "correct_answer": "The Bourne Ultimatum and Bourne Supremacy", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bourne Identity and The Bourne Ultimatum", "The Bourne Supremacy", "The Bourne Chase"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the diet of the platypus?", "correct_answer": "Platypuses are carnivores.", "incorrect_answers": ["Platypuses are herbivores.", "Platypuses are specialized eaters.", "Platypuses are omnivores."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Chinatown, how did Jakes operatives tell what time Mulray drove away?", "correct_answer": "They placed watches under his tires.", "incorrect_answers": ["They asked his wife.", "They put a microphone in his backseat.", "They kept constant observation."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal is the primary host of the protozoan Toxoplasma gondii which causes toxoplasmosis?", "correct_answer": "Cat", "incorrect_answers": ["Pigeon", "Fly", "Dog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Naruto Uzumaki, the protagonist of the Naruto series, marries Sakura.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Hollywood actress appeared in the 1961 movie Judgment at Nuremberg?", "correct_answer": "Marlene Dietrich", "incorrect_answers": ["Grace Kelly", "Greta Garbo", "Audrey Hepburn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "New Zealand was the first country to give full voting rights to women.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is used in the movie Lucky Number Slevin for a situation in which everybody looks left and you move right?", "correct_answer": "Kansas City Shuffle", "incorrect_answers": ["Boise Bounce Out", "Toronto Tap Out", "New Orleans Boogie"]}]